Guide to the Dorothy Norman Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Pre-1990 Acquisitions, 1908-1983; 2; 25.25; 28 boxes
  - Dorothy Norman Correspondence
    - Novack, George, 1941-1942 (Box 77)
    - Novell, Elizabeth, 1937-1938 (Box 77)
    - NRF (Firm), 1938-1939 (Box 77)
    - Nuhn, Ferner, 1938-1939 (Box 77)
    - "O" General, 1934-1938 (Box 77)
    - O'Brien, Edward, 1938-1941 (Box 77)
    - Ocampo, Victoria, 1937-1941 (Box 77)
    - O'Connor, John, 1947 March 18 (Box 77)
    - Odets, Clifford, 1937-1946, undated (Box 77)
    - Of, George F., 1947 December 4 (Box 77)
    - Oko, Dorothy, 1948 January 9 (Box 77)
    - Olivet College Book Store, 1938 (Box 77)
    - Olson, Charles, 1937-1946, undated (Box 77)
    - O'Neill, Eugene, 1937-1941 (Box 77)
    - O'Neill, Hugh A., undated (Box 77)
    - Oprecht, Emil, 1938-1939 (Box 77)
    - Osborn, Fairfield, 1950-1954, undated (Box 77)
    - Oswald, Marianne, 1946, undated (Box 77)
    - Ottley, Roi, 1944 (Box 77)
    - "P" General, 1938-1957, undated (Box 77)
    - Pach, Walter, 1937-1954, undated (Box 77)
    - Padover, Saul Kussiel, 1951-1958 (Box 77)
    - Page, Christina, 1945-1948 (Box 77)
    - Palmer, Carleton H., 1949 January 3 (Box 77)
    - Palmer, George Anthony, 1937-1938 (Box 77)
    - Palmer, Robert, 1946, undated (Box 77)
    - Pandit, Krishna, Lekha, Raja & Rita, 1944-1956; 2 (Box 77)
    - Parker, Mr., 1946 November 1 (Box 77)
    - Parran, Thomas, 1938 (Box 77)
    - Parsons, Elsie Worthington Clews, 1938 (Box 77)
    - Partisan Review, 1939, undated (Box 77)
    - Patchen, Kenneth, 1937-1944, undated (Box 77)
    - Paulhan, Jean, 1937-1940 (Box 77)
    - Pearce, Charles A., 1937-1947 (Box 77)
    - Peggram, Reed Edward, 1938-1941, undated (Box 77)
    - Pellegrini & Cudahy, 1947-1959, undated (Box 77)
    - Pemberton, Brock, undated (Box 77)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1947-1954 (Box 77)
    - Pereda, Prudencio de, 1939-1941 (Box 77)
    - Perera, Dorothy, 1938-1940, undated (Box 77)
    - Perlès, Alfred, 1937-1939 (Box 77)
    - Perry, Bernard B., 1952-1955 (Box 77)
    - Perry, Donald I., 1956-1961 (Box 77)
    - Perry, Leslie S., 1948 (Box 77)
    - Perry, Ralph Barton, 1937-1938 (Box 77)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1948-1969 (Box 77)
    - Phillips, Duncan & Marjorie, 1946-1947 (Box 77)
    - Phillips, Leslie Gordon, 1950-1951, undated (Box 77)
    - Photogravure and Color Company, 1953 December 14 (Box 77)
    - Picabia, Madam, 1954 March 5 (Box 77)
    - Pickett, Clarence, 1938-1941 (Box 77)
    - Pilot Press, 1946-1947 (Box 77)
    - Pilpel, Harriet F., 1938-1947, undated (Box 77)
    - Pink, Louis H., 1945 (Box 77)
    - Piotrowski, Zygmunt, 1938 (Box 77)
    - Piscator, Erwin & Maria, 1941-1948 (Box 77)
    - Pitts, Rebecca E., 1937-1941 (Box 77)
    - Pittsburgh Salon of Photography, undated (Box 77)
    - P M Daily, 1943-1948 (Box 77)
    - Poetry Magazine, 1938-1939, undated (Box 77)
    - Politzer, Heinz, 1938-1939 (Box 77)
    - Pollitzer, Anita, 1947, undated (Box 77)
    - Polack, J. H., 1941 (Box 77)
    - Pollak, Franklin, 1939-1942 (Box 77)
    - Pond, Cordelia Sargent, 1948 January 9 (Box 77)
    - Popular Photography, 1948 (Box 77)
    - Porter, Aline & Eliot, 1946-1959 (Box 77)
    - Porter, Fairfield, 1947 June 28 (Box 77)
    - Porter, Harriette Wilbur, 1941 (Box 77)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne, 1937-1938 (Box 77)
    - Post, C. Gordon (Charles Gordon), 1941 (Box 77)
    - Poulos, Constantine, 1939 (Box 77)
    - Pouzzner, Bessie L., 1947 November 21 (Box 77)
    - Powell, Clarence Alva, 1941-1948 (Box 77)
    - Powers, Marcella, 1946-1947 (Box 77)
    - Pozner, Vladimir, 1941-1942 (Box 77)
    - Pratt Institute, 1961-1963 (Box 77)
    - Prescott, Joseph, 1940 (Box 77)
    - Preston, John Hyde, 1937 (Box 77)
    - Princeton University Press, 1938 (Box 77)
    - Printers' Ink, 1949 January 7 (Box 77)
    - Prosser, Margaret, 1947-1951 (Box 77)
    - Prombaum, Sophie, 1940-1943 (Box 77)
    - Pucciani, Oreste F., 1947-1948 (Box 77)
    - Puma, Fernando, 1946-1947 (Box 77)
    - Purcell, Gray, 1948, undated (Box 77)
    - Putnam, Phelps, 1937 (Box 77)
    - "Q" General, 1938-1946 (Box 77)
    - Querido Verlag, 1937-1938 (Box 77)
    - Quinn, John, 1947 November 25 (Box 77)
    - Quinn, Kerker, 1938-1941, undated (Box 77)
    - Quittner, G. F., 1947 December 11 (Box 77)
    - "R" General, 1934-1948, undated (Box 78)
    - Rabinowitch, Joseph, 1937-1946 (Box 78)
    - Radhakrishnan, S. (Sarvepalli), 1953-1955 (Box 78)
    - Rahv, Philip, 1939-1944 (Box 78)
    - Rainer, Luise, 1938-1957, undated (Box 78)
    - Raiziss, Sona, 1938 (Box 78)
    - Rajagopalachari, C. (Chakravarti), 1950-1954, undated (Box 78)
    - Raja Singam, S. Durai, 1952-1953 (Box 78)
    - Rand McNally and Company, 1939 (Box 78)
    - Randolph-Macon Woman's College, 1949 January 6 (Box 78)
    - Random House, Inc., 1938-1947 (Box 78)
    - Rao, Raja, 1951-1954, undated (Box 78)
    - Rao, Shanta, 1955-1963, undated (Box 78)
    - Ratliff, Beulah Amidon, 1937 (Box 78)
    - Raymund, Bernard, 1946-1947, undated (Box 78)
    - Read, Herbert, 1946 (Box 78)
    - Reddick, Lawrence Dunbar, 1946, undated (Box 78)
    - Reehl Litho Company, 1939 (Box 78)
    - Rehm, Mary Torr, 1948, undated (Box 78)
    - Reis, Arthur M., 1938 (Box 78)
    - Reis, Lincoln, 1937-1938 (Box 78)
    - Reis, Rebecca, 1939, undated (Box 78)
    - Reiss, Lionel S. (Lionel Samson), 1946 December 18 (Box 78)
    - Replansky, Naomi, 1945-1948 (Box 78)
    - Revista Devenir, 1949 (Box 78)
    - Rhoades, Katharine N., 1946-1948 (Box 78)
    - Rice, Virginia, 1937 (Box 78)
    - Rich, Daniel Catton, 1946-1947 (Box 78)
    - Richards, Carol, 1941, undated (Box 78)
    - Richardson, Dorothy, 1939, undated (Box 78)
    - Richman, Robert, 1952 (Box 78)
    - Richter, Hans, 1944-1958, undated (Box 78)
    - Riding, Laura, 1937, undated (Box 78)
    - Rie, Robert, 1939-1946 (Box 78)
    - Riesel, Victor, 1941-1942, undated (Box 78)
    - Riesman, Evelyn & David, 1939-1959, undated (Box 78)
    - Riley, Maude Kemper, 1946-1947 (Box 78)
    - Ringel, Fred J. (Fred Julius), 1937-1947 (Box 78)
    - Ritter, Christl, 1939-1946 (Box 78)
    - Roberts, Donald A., 1950 (Box 78)
    - Robertson, Constance Noyes, 1938 (Box 78)
    - Robinson, Edward G., 1958, undated (Box 78)
    - Robinson, Florence H., 1948-1949 (Box 78)
    - Robinson, T. C., 1938-1940 (Box 78)
    - Rockefeller, John, Jr., 1946 September 3 (Box 78)
    - Rodakiewicz, Henwar, 1940-1949 (Box 78)
    - Roditi, Edouard, 1939-1940, undated (Box 78)
    - Rodman, Selden, 1939, undated (Box 78)
    - Rolo, Charles, 1949 (Box 78)
    - Rome, Harold, 1938 (Box 78)
    - Ronnebeck, Louise, 1949 (Box 78)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1939-1962, undated (Box 78)
    - Rosenbaum, Ira, 1937, undated (Box 78)
    - Rosenfeld, Paul, 1936-1947; 2 (Box 78)
      Includes photographs, newspaper clippings and other printed material relating to Paul Rosenfeld.
    - Roskolenko, Harry, 1937-1945 (Box 78)
    - Ross, Cary, 1932-1938, undated; 2 (Box 78)
    - Ross, E. A., 1938 (Box 78)
    - Rothschild, Alix, baroness de, 1954-1962, undated (Box 78)
    - Rothschild, Bethsabée de, baroness, 1957-1958 (Box 78)
    - Rougemont, Denis de, 1941-1947, undated (Box 78)
    - Rounseville, Robert, 1951, undated (Box 78)
    - Rudd, Martin, 1938, undated (Box 78)
    - Rugg, Harold, 1937-1947 (Box 78)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1937-1946, undated (Box 78)
    - Rusk, William Sener, 1939-1943, undated (Box 78)
    - Ryan, W. Carson (Will Carson), 1938 (Box 78)
    - Ryserson, Edward, 1941-1947, undated (Box 78)
    - "S" General, 1934-1955, undated (Box 79)
    - Sachs, Alexander, 1938-1940, undated (Box 79)
    - Sahgal, Gautam & Tara, 1950-1957, undated (Box 79)
    - Saint-Gaudens, Homer, 1947 May 27 (Box 79)
    - Saint-John Perse, 1950-1956 (Box 79)
    - Salinas, Marcel, 1958-1959 (Box 79)
    - Salmony, A. (Alfred), 1950-1957, undated (Box 79)
    - Salsamendi, A., 1960-1962 (Box 79)
    - Salt, Sidney, 1940, undated (Box 79)
    - Salter, L. J., 1939-1946 (Box 79)
    - Salvemini, Gaetano, 1939-1944 (Box 79)
    - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, 1950 (Box 79)
    - Samson, Hugh, 1940-1941 (Box 79)
    - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1947-1958 (Box 79)
    - Sanger, Margaret, 1937-1952 (Box 79)
    - Santayara, George, 1937 (Box 79)
    - Sargent, Porter, 1939-1943 (Box 79)
    - Saroyan, William, 1937-1941, undated (Box 79)
    - Sartre, Jean-Paul, 1946-1948 (Box 79)
    - Saturday Review of Literature, 1949 (Box 79)
    - Saunders, Marion, 1937-1941 (Box 79)
    - Savage, Leonard J., 1947 (Box 79)
    - Schack, William, 1940-1941 (Box 79)
    - Schaefer, Alice, 1940-1949 (Box 79)
    - Schafer, Roger, undated (Box 79)
    - Schapiro, Meyer, 1937-1939 (Box 79)
    - Scheler, Michael B., 1933-1943 (Box 79)
    - Schiffer, Sidney, 1951 (Box 79)
    - Schiffman, Joseph, 1950-1951 (Box 79)
    - Schnee, Charlotte R., 1939 (Box 79)
    - Schneider, Alexander, 1953-1954, undated (Box 79)
    - Schnitzler, Heinrich & Olga, 1939-1942, undated (Box 79)
    - Schocken Books Inc., 1947 (Box 79)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold, 1938 (Box 79)
    - Scholastic Magazines, 1947 December 23 (Box 79)
    - Schorer, Mark, 1940, undated (Box 79)
    - Schroeder, Theo, 1940, undated (Box 79)
    - Schubart, Dorothy, 1946-1949 (Box 79)
    - Schubart, Selma Stieglitz, 1946-1949, undated; 2 (Box 79)
    - Schubart, William Howard, 1941-1942, undated (Box 79)
    - Schubert, David, 1938, undated (Box 79)
    - Schuman, Frederick L. (Frederick Lewis), 1941-1946 (Box 79)
    - Schuman, Robert, 1943 (Box 79)
    - Schuman, William, 1938-1940, undated (Box 79)
    - Schuster, M. Lincoln (Max Lincoln), 1946 (Box 79)
    - Schwab, Arthur, 1948 January 13 (Box 79)
    - Schwartz, Delmore, 1937-1939 (Box 79)
    - Schweitzer, Albert, 1937 (Box 79)
    - Schwimmer, Rosika, 1937-1939 (Box 79)
    - Scott, Evelyn, 1937-1939, undated (Box 79)
    - Scott, Nathan, 1951 (Box 79)
    - Seaver, Edwin, 1938-1941, undated (Box 79)
    - Seaver, Esther Isabel, 1941-1943 (Box 79)
    - Seff, Manuel, 1946 (Box 79)
    - Seidenberg, Roderick, 1938, undated (Box 79)
    - Seldes, George, 1939, undated (Box 79)
    - Seldes, Gilbert, 1938-1940, undated (Box 79)
    - Sele Art, 1952-1953 (Box 79)
      Includes correspondence relating to Sele Art.
    - Seligmann, André, 1947 December 22 (Box 79)
    - Seligmann, Herbert J. (Herbert Jacob), 1939-1947 (Box 79)
    - Selvin, Paul, 1947-1948 (Box 79)
    - Selz, Peter, 1958-1963, undated (Box 79)
    - Sereno, Renzo, 1939 (Box 79)
    - Sergel, Roger, 1937 (Box 79)
    - Sessions, Roger, 1937-1940, undated (Box 79)
    - Seven, 1939, undated (Box 79)
    - Seward, William, 1942-1945 (Box 79)
    - Seyd, Felizia, 1939-1940, undated (Box 79)
    - Shand, William, 1945-1946 (Box 79)
    - Shapira, Nathan, 1958-1963 (Box 79)
    - Sharp, Mary, 1949 January 3 (Box 79)
    - Shaw, George Bernard, 1938-1951 (Box 79)
    - Shaw, Irwin, 1937-1939 (Box 79)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 1948, undated (Box 79)
    - Sheyne, Mikhail, 1940-1954; 2 (Box 79)
    - Shinn, Walter Scott, 1947 March 13 (Box 79)
    - Shipley, Joseph, 1940-1941 (Box 79)
    - Schultz, L. B., 1937 (Box 79)
    - Sibley, Charles, 1939 (Box 79)
    - Silone, Ignazio & Darina, 1937-1954 (Box 79)
    - Silva, Anil de, 1958-1960, undated (Box 79)
    - Simonson, Lee, 1947 February 27 (Box 79)
    - Singer, Caroline, 1939, undated (Box 79)
    - Singh, Madanjeet, 1952-1957 (Box 79)
    - Singh, Sirdar J. J., 1946-1958, undated (Box 79)
    - Sipley, Lewis Walton, 1954 April 29 (Box 79)
    - Slochower, Harry, 1939-1946 (Box 79)
    - Slonimsky, Nicolas, 1938 (Box 79)
    - Slotnikoff, Will, 1937-1939, undated (Box 79)
    - Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1938 (Box 79)
    - Smith, Lillian, 1944-1958, undated (Box 80)
    - Smith, Robert Paul, 1938-1940, undated (Box 80)
    - Smith, T. V., 1938 (Box 80)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1947 December 29 (Box 80)
    - Soby, James Thrall, 1947 November 1 (Box 80)
    - Social Frontier, 1938-1939 (Box 80)
    - Sonnenberg, Benjamin, 1947, undated (Box 80)
    - The Southern Review, 1938-1939 (Box 80)
    - Sparks, William Sheppard, 1947 December 18 (Box 80)
    - Speiser, Maurice J. (Maurice Joseph), 1940-1946 (Box 80)
    - Spender, Stephen, 1937-1955, undated (Box 80)
    - Spingarn, Arthur B. (Arthur Barnett), 1940 (Box 80)
    - Spivacke, Harold, 1938 (Box 80)
    - Spoerri, Viviane, 1948 (Box 80)
    - Sprinchorn, Carl, 1954 August 10 (Box 80)
    - Stark, Irwin, 1941-1946 (Box 80)
    - Stark, John, 1946 (Box 80)
    - Stearns, Milton S., 1953, undated (Box 80)
    - Stecker, Louise, 1948 January 19 (Box 80)
    - Steichen, Edward, 1942-1951, undated (Box 80)
    - Stein, Gertrude, 1937-1947 (Box 80)
    - Stein, Leo, 1946-1947, undated (Box 80)
    - Steinberg, Saul & Sterne, Hedda, 1950-1952, undated (Box 80)
    - Stern, Leo, 1947-1948 (Box 80)
    - Stettheimer, Ettie, 1946-1947 (Box 80)
    - Stevens, Edward S., 1948 (Box 80)
    - Stewart, C. I., 1938 (Box 80)
    - Stewart, Dorothy N. (Dorothy Newkirk), 1947 December 18 (Box 80)
    - Stiefel, Babette, 1945-1948 (Box 80)
    - Stieglitz, Mrs. Albert H., 1947 June 12 (Box 80)
    - Stieglitz, Edward, 1953 December 3 (Box 80)
    - Stieglitz, Julius, 1953 (Box 80)
    - Stieglitz, Leopold, 1944-1946, undated (Box 80)
    - Stilwell, Elsie, 1948 (Box 80)
    - Stoloff, Carolyn, 1948 (Box 80)
    - Straight, John H., 1952-1955 (Box 80)
    - Straight, Michael, 1941-1942 (Box 80)
    - Strand, Paul, 1937-1948 (Box 80)
    - Strasser, John A., 1938, undated (Box 80)
    - Straus, Flora, undated (Box 80)
    - Straus, Roger, 1950-1964 (Box 80)
    - Stravinsky, Igor, 1940 January 3 (Box 80)
    - Studebaker, J. W. (John Ward), 1938-1939 (Box 80)
    - Summers, V. T., 1947 (Box 80)
    - Sussman, Aaron, 1952 (Box 80)
    - Sutton, Eric, 1947 (Box 80)
    - Swallow, Alan, 1941-1942 (Box 80)
    - Swan, Emmy, 1937-1941 (Box 80)
    - Swan, Maurice, 1940-1945, undated (Box 80)
    - Sweeney, James Johnson, 1946-1948 (Box 80)
    - Swing, Raymond, 1953-1954 (Box 80)
    - Sykes, Gerald, 1937-1957, undated; 2 (Box 80)
    - "T" General, 1935-1951, undated (Box 80)
    - Taft, Robert, 1946 November 26 (Box 80)
    - Tagliacozzo, Enzo, 1944 (Box 80)
    - Taglicht, Edith, 1940 (Box 80)
    - Talmadge, Irving DeWitt, 1938-1939 (Box 80)
    - Tate, Allen, 1937 (Box 80)
    - Tausig, Mrs. Karl, 1952 (Box 80)
    - Taylor, Francis Henry, 1946 November 7 (Box 80)
    - Taylor, Harold, 1950-1959 (Box 80)
    - Taylor, Prentiss, 1937 (Box 80)
    - Teall, Dorothy, 1937-1940, undated (Box 80)
    - Tennant, John, 1948-1949 (Box 80)
    - Thierry, James Francis, 1937 (Box 80)
    - Thoma, Richard, 1937-1939, undated (Box 80)
    - Thomas, Dylan, 1938 February 19 (Box 80)
    - Thomas, Evan, 1938 (Box 80)
    - Thomas, Lenoire, 1937 (Box 80)
    - Thomas, Norman, 1938-1954, undated (Box 80)
    - Thompson, Arthur, 1943, undated (Box 80)
    - Thompson, David, 1951 October 17 (Box 80)
    - Thompson, Dorothy, 1938-1942 (Box 80)
    - Time Magazine, 1946-1949 (Box 80)
    - Todd, Edwin, 1941-1945 (Box 80)
    - Todrin, Boris, 1937 (Box 80)
    - Tofel, Jennings, 1937-1948, undated (Box 80)
    - Toller, Ernst, 1937-1939 (Box 80)
    - Tolstoy, Alexandra, 1941 (Box 80)
    - Toomer, Jean, 1938-1947 (Box 80)
    - Town Hall, Inc., 1938 (Box 80)
    - Townsend, Willard S., 1945 (Box 80)
    - Toynbee, Arnold, 1937 (Box 80)
    - Tozier, Roy, 1940-1941, undated (Box 80)
    - Trager, Frank, 1940-1941 (Box 80)
    - Trowbridge, W. D., 1939 (Box 80)
    - True, Dorothy, 1948, undated (Box 80)
    - Tucci, Nicolo, 1947, undated (Box 80)
    - Turnbull, Eleanor, 1940-1947 (Box 80)
    - Tyler, Parker, 1937-1941 (Box 80)
    - Tzara, Tristan, 1953-1954 (Box 80)
    - "U" General, 1938-1963, undated (Box 80)
    - Uhse, Bob, 1939, undated (Box 80)
    - Union Review, 1940 (Box 80)
    - United States. Department of the Treasury, 1951 December 19 (Box 80)
    - United States International Book Association, 1946-1947, undated (Box 80)
    - University of Minnesota, 1947 (Box 80)
    - University of Rochester. Memorial Art Gallery, 1947 (Box 80)
    - Untermeyer, Louis, 1939-1941 (Box 80)
    - Urquhart, Fred, 1940-1942, undated (Box 80)
    - U. S. Camera, 1947 (Box 80)
    - "V" General, 1937-1947, undated (Box 80)
    - Vallentin, Antonina, 1948-1956, undated (Box 80)
    - Vanderlyn, Leon, 1941, undated (Box 80)
    - Van Doren, Carl, 1946 September 7 (Box 80)
    - Vanguard Booksellers, 1942-1943 (Box 80)
    - Van Landigham, Adelaide, 1949, undated (Box 80)
    - Van Loan, Dorothy, 1948, undated (Box 80)
    - Van Norman, Mabel, 1948 (Box 80)
    - Van Vechten, Carl, 1947-1952, undated; 2 (Box 80)
    - Varese, Edgar & Louise, 1938-1947, undated (Box 80)
    - Venturi, Lionello, 1946-1947 (Box 80)
    - Victoria and Albert Museum, 1947 June 17 (Box 80)
    - Viertel, Berthold, 1946 (Box 80)
    - Viking Press, 1938-1947, undated (Box 80)
    - Villa, José García, 1949-1959, undated (Box 80)
    - Villard, Léonie, 1937 (Box 80)
    - Vinton, Warren Jay, 1938 (Box 80)
    - Vladeck, B. (Baruch), 1937-1938 (Box 80)
    - "W" General, 1937-1949, undated (Box 80)
    - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1947 March 7 (Box 80)
    - Wagner, Elizabeth Archibald, 1937, undated (Box 80)
    - Walden School, 1941 (Box 80)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 1946-1947 (Box 80)
    - Walsh, Mary R., 1939-1940 (Box 80)
    - Walt Whitman School, 1941 (Box 80)
    - War Department, 1947-1948 (Box 81)
    - Ward, Harry Frederick, 1938 (Box 81)
    - Warner, Keith, 1946-1953, undated (Box 81)
    - Washington Post, 1947-1948 (Box 81)
    - Webb, M. J., 1952 (Box 81)
    - Webb, Todd, 1942-1947, undated (Box 81)
    - Weber, Brom, 1940-1955, undated (Box 81)
    - Webster, Harvey Curtis, 1940-1941 (Box 81)
    - Weeks, Edward, 1947 March 20 (Box 81)
    - Weichsel, Florence K., 1947 June 24 (Box 81)
    - Weigel, Henrietta, 1940 (Box 81)
    - Weinberg, Mr., 1949 February 10 (Box 81)
    - Weinberger, Harry, 1939 (Box 81)
    - Weinstein, Charles C., 1941-1943 (Box 81)
    - Weiss, Alma, 1949 March 7 (Box 81)
    - Weiss, Paul, 1938-1939 (Box 81)
    - Weitzman, Bernard, 1948-1949 (Box 81)
    - Welles, Mary, 1940-1941, undated (Box 81)
    - Wells, Cady, 1947 (Box 81)
    - Wertham, Fredric, 1946 (Box 81)
    - Wertheim, Maurice, 1948 January 15 (Box 81)
    - Wescott, Glenway, 1937 (Box 81)
    - Westerfield, Hargis, 1945, undated (Box 81)
    - Weston, Brett, 1952-1955, undated (Box 81)
    - Weston, Dorothy & Edward, 1946-1951, undated (Box 81)
    - Wheeler, Emily L., 1947-1949 (Box 81)
    - Wheeler, Monroe, 1937-1947, undated (Box 81)
    - Wheelwright, John, 1931-1937 (Box 81)
    - Wheelwright, Mary, 1947 March 10 (Box 81)
    - Whipple, Leon, 1938-1941 (Box 81)
    - White, Clarence H., 1947-1948 (Box 81)
    - White, Katherine Anne, 1946-1947 (Box 81)
    - White, Kenneth, 1937-1938 (Box 81)
    - White, Minor, 1953-1957 (Box 81)
    - Whitehead, Alfred North, 1937-1938 (Box 81)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1947-1954 (Box 81)
    - Who's Who in America, 1947 July 11 (Box 81)
    - Whyte Bookshop, 1939 (Box 81)
    - Wiener, Alma, 1946, undated (Box 81)
    - Wight, Frederick, circa 1955-1961 (Box 81)
    - Wilder, Charlotte, 1937-1940 (Box 81)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1940 (Box 81)
    - Williams, Oscar, 1938-1941 (Box 81)
    - Williams, Ruth, 1938-1941, undated (Box 81)
    - Williams, William Carlos, 1937-1958 (Box 81)
    - Wills, Arthur, 1938-1939 (Box 81)
    - Wilson, Edmund, 1937-1947 (Box 81)
    - Wilson, Gilbert, 1939 (Box 81)
    - Wilson, Mildred, 1940, undated (Box 81)
    - Wilson, Rosalind, 1952 (Box 81)
    - Winston, Lydia, 1946-1949, undated (Box 81)
    - Winston, Richard, 1946 (Box 81)
    - Wise, James Waterman, 1943 (Box 81)
    - Wise, Raymond, 1939 (Box 81)
    - Wise, Stephen, 1939 (Box 81)
    - Withington, Robert, 1938-1939 (Box 81)
    - Witkin, Dick, 1940 (Box 81)
    - Wittenborn, G., 1947 March 19 (Box 81)
    - Wolf, Victoria, 1941, undated (Box 81)
    - Wolff, Helen, 1941-1942 (Box 81)
    - Wolff, Kurt, 1941-1946 (Box 81)
    - Woodburn, John, 1946-1948 (Box 81)
    - Woodring, Carl R., 1947, undated (Box 81)
    - Woods, Glennyth M., 1945-1949 (Box 81)
    - Worcester Art Museum, 1948-1949 (Box 81)
    - Worth, Marie, 1942-1945, undated (Box 81)
    - Wright, Cedric, 1948, undated (Box 81)
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1937-1948 (Box 81)
    - Wright, George, 1955-1956 (Box 81)
    - Wright, Mary Buckland, 1938 (Box 81)
    - Wright, Richard, circa 1946-1956 (Box 81)
    - Wurst, Margarethe, 1943, undated (Box 81)
    - Württembergische Landesbibliothek. Hölderlin-Archiv, 1952 (Box 81)
    - W. W. Norton & Company, 1941-1946 (Box 81)
    - "Y" General, 1939-1940, undated (Box 81)
    - Yarmolinsky, Avrahm, 1938-1939 (Box 81)
    - Yergan, Max, 1939 (Box 81)
    - Yorck, Ruth, 1939-1964, undated (Box 81)
    - Young, Anita, 1948 January 4 (Box 81)
    - Young, Art, 1937 (Box 81)
    - Young, Frederic H., 1946-1948 (Box 81)
    - Young, Nancy, 1953, undated (Box 81)
    - "Z" General, 1938-1947 (Box 81)
    - Zeisler, Richard, 1950-1955, undated (Box 81)
    - Zigrosser, Carl, 1937-1948, undated (Box 81)
    - Zimmer, Henry R., 1940-1941 (Box 81)
    - Zirinsky, Julius, 1947 (Box 81)
    - Zoler, Emil, 1946-1954, undated (Box 81)
    - Zorach, William, 1941 December 30 (Box 81)
    - Zukerman, William, 1939-1942 (Box 81)
    - Zukofsky, Louis, 1938-1941 (Box 81)
    - Zutski, C. N., 1953 (Box 81)
    - Zimmer, A., 1938-1939 (Box 81)
    - Zylberg, Helene, 1948, undated (Box 81)
    - Unsorted correspondence, circa 1928-1946 (Box 81)
  - Alfred Stieglitz Correspondence
    Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
    Alfred Stieglitz Correspondence holds only photostats and typed transcripts of letters, most of which are held in the Beinecke Library's Alfred Stieglitz/Georgia O'Keeffe Archive (YCAL MSS 85).
    - Excerpts of letters, undated; 3 (Box 82)
    - "A" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Anderson, Sherwood, undated (Box 82)
    - "B" General, undated (Box 82)
    - "C" General, undated (Box 82)
    - "D" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Demuth, Charles, undated (Box 82)
    - "E" General, undated (Box 82)
    - "F" General, undated (Box 82)
    - "G" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Goldberg, Elias, undated (Box 82)
    - "H" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Ház, Nicholas, undated (Box 82)
    - "I" General, undated (Box 82)
    - "K" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Kalonyme, Louis K., undated (Box 82)
    - Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Co., undated (Box 82)
    - "L" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Lachaise, Gaston, undated (Box 82)
    - Lamb, Beatrice, undated (Box 82)
    - Levy, Julien, undated (Box 82)
    - Luhan, Mabel Dodge, undated (Box 82)
    - "M" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Margules, De Hirsh, undated (Box 82)
    - Mellquist, Jerome, undated (Box 82)
    - "N" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Nikhilananda, Swami, undated (Box 82)
    - Norman, Nancy, undated (Box 82)
    - "O" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Pelikan, G., undated (Box 82)
    - "R" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Ritter, Christl, undated (Box 82)
    - Roberts, Donell E., undated (Box 82)
    - Rodakiewicz, Henwar, undated (Box 82)
    - "S" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Schubart, Dorothy, undated (Box 82)
    - Schubart, Selma Stieglitz, undated (Box 82)
    - Sykes, Gerald, undated (Box 82)
    - "T" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Tofel, Jennings, undated (Box 82)
    - "U-V" General, undated (Box 82)
    - "W" General, undated (Box 82)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, undated (Box 82)
    - Winston, Lydia, undated (Box 82)
    - Williams, Clifford, undated (Box 82)
    - Young, William, undated (Box 82)
    - Zoler, Emil, undated (Box 82)
    - Zigrosser, Carl, undated (Box 82)